Three years ago, on that day,
I took the First Steps entrance exam.
You better remember this.
My name is Luke.
I am Luke Sykol,
the invincible divine blade,
the Testament Blade!
Don't worry.
You are strong.
However, I was stronger.
That's all it is.
Thus I, Chloe Welter, failed that exam.
Afterward, I gave up on trying
to become a hunter.
I keep my watchful eye on
the hunters' activities
as the receptionist of the
Explorers' Association.
Hello, and welcome to the Association!
I knew I'd heard of him somewhere.
Crashing Lightning, Arnold Hail...
So he's a level 7, you say?
Yes.
While they were not entirely blameless,
it's a bit of a problem that we
immediately antagonized them.
I hope the shock of being pummeled
made him forget everything...
Crashing Lightning is credited with
having vanquished a thunder dragon.
We should settle this peacefully.
Let's have Branch Manager
Gark smooth this over.
I'll contact him.
Yeah, please do.
That thunder dragon, though...
They're pretty tasty with teriyaki sauce.
Teriyaki, you say?
Yeah.
Sitri's made it for me before.
Now I've got a craving for it.
E-Every part of the thunder
dragon is rare and valuable.
I've never heard of it being used
as a cooking ingredient.
Yeah, I know. I get it.
I was just thinking it would
be nice if we had some.
Don't mind me.
Damn it!
That woman... We can't let
her get away with this!
She is strong.
She's probably quite a famous
hunter in the capital.
But it won't end like this.
She will regret besmirching
the name of the Falling Fog!
Stop, Drink!
Enough of your mischief!
Got... you!
Wait, ow!
Stop struggling!
"The Falling Fog Wants Revenge."
Episode 11
The Falling Fog Wants Revenge
Let This Grieving Soul Retire
We're not here out of grievance!
You're not?
I heard you got kicked into
next Tuesday in the pub,
so I was certain you were
here to file a complaint.
Why you...!
We only came to find out
the name of that woman.
With her godly speed, she
doesn't even cast a shadow.
Stifled Shadow, Liz Smart.
Who are you?
Gark, the branch manager.
I've heard the rumors, Crashing Lightning.
You had a rough time just
after you arrived, huh?
I tried to have her guardian
put the brakes on them all...
Looks like he completely forgot.
What did you say?!
He was at the pub, right?
He might have seemed a bit out of it,
or easygoing, perhaps.
Thousand Tricks, Krai Andrey.
He's level 8.
That guy?!
Level 8?!
Don't worry.
He's not one to allow anyone
to bully weaker people.
If you guys behave yourselves,
I'm sure he won't let Liz
lay a hand on you again.
Oh, right.
It looks like Thousand Tricks
has a request for you guys.
Let's see...
It says, "It's really good
with teriyaki sauce,
so please bring back some
thunder dragon meat."
Whether you take the mission
or not is up to you.
I wish you the best of luck, Dragon Slayers.
What are we going to do, Arnold?
Everyone, get ready.
Our target is Thousand Tricks!
Is it true that you have a debt
with Sitri in the upper ten digits?
Yes, yes. It's true.
You do realize how much that is, right?
Of course I do.
Let's see.
One, ten, one hundred,
one thousand, ten thousand,
hundred thousand, a million, ten million...
In other words, you owe
almost ten billion.
So what did Sitri say about that?
She proposed three possible solutions.
The first one is that you throw me
into prison, thus avoiding repayment.
I'd be very lonely all by myself, though,
so be sure to lock up my
older sister with me, too.
No, no.
You haven't done anything wrong,
so why would you go to jail?
What's your second idea?
Option two is that I become your wife.
What?!
If we're married,
we can unify all our assets.
If we did that, your debt would
naturally vanish, as well.
And what's option three?
That you become my husband.
It looks like the only
option is getting married!
Krai!
It's a joke.
I plan to pay her back.
As long as you're not wasteful,
your income from the Grievers should
be sufficient for eventual repayment.
If you want to pay her
back quicker than that,
why not venture into a treasure
vault by yourself sometime?
You're telling me to go die?
I'll put together a repayment plan for you.
In the meantime, just make sure to
not incur any more debt, please.
Got it?!
Yes, got it.
That said, it's almost auction time.
Someone who can see the future...
I hear that's the kind of
man Thousand Tricks is.
Rumors say he reached level 8
without ever making a mistake.
At any rate, he's supposed to be incredible.
Master is a god!
It looks like no matter who you ask,
everyone only gives vague answers.
Anyway, he's a man full of mystery.
And it seems he rarely participates in trips
to the treasure vaults these days,
leaving it all to his party.
There're outrageous rumors of him manifesting
a treasure vault in front of everyone,
or sending a huge golem
flying with his willpower alone.
These are silly tall tales.
When nobody knows what's real,
things always get exaggerated.
For a level 8 to look like that,
be spoken of only in vague rumors,
and leave all treasure vaults
to his party instead...
Could it be...
that he doesn't have combat
skills to fit his level?
Now that you mention it,
there were a few testimonies stating that
they've never seen him in an actual fight.
I'm starting to get the picture now.
He's likely more of a tactician.
He didn't reach level 8
with his own strength,
but thanks to his party members.
So he himself is...
I wouldn't say he's weak.
But he's no match for me, someone
who reached level 7 on his own merit.
You're right!
That's our Arnold!
They looked down on us as hicks.
We'll show the people of this capital.
I'm going to defeat your precious Level 8.
A debt in the upper ten digits...
Even with Eva taking care
of the repayment plan...
No, never mind that!
This weather's so nice.
If only I could forget everything
and dissolve into the air.
Master!
Huh?
Is there something you need from me?
What?
When I looked up into the sky,
I saw you smiling down at me.
She saw that from below?
You can ask me anything at all!
For you, I'd do anything!
Well then... um...
I got fooled, again.
What do you take me for, Master?
I didn't trick you. I really didn't.
So, how much money do you require?
I-I mean, I also need money
for restocking my items
and the maintenance of my equipment...
So there's a limit to what I can do...
No, no, I was just saying stuff.
I don't intend to borrow money from you.
It's an upper ten-digit debt, after all.
Ten... digit?
One, ten, one hundred,
one thousand, ten thousand,
one hundred thousand,
one million, ten million...
I-Impressive as ever, Master...
To think there's someone who
lent you that much money...
I knew everybody should be in awe of you.
I'm telling you, it's fine.
Sitri's the one I'm borrowing from,
and if it comes down to it,
we'll get married, and it'll be even.
M-M-Married?!
Not Sitri!
She'll definitely try to
have him all for herself!
It's just a joke.
We won't be able to go on
walks together anymore!
Since you're here, why don't we
go get something sweet together?
My treat.
Ah, sometimes we humans just
need to go outside for a bit.
Master, I've been thinking.
Huh? About what?
The debt.
The ten digits.
O-Oh, that.
Why don't we go look for
relics in treasure vaults?
The auction's just around the corner,
so maybe you could sell them for a good price.
So Tino wants me to die, too?
You probably know which treasure
vaults hold valuable relics.
Who the hell do you think I am?
If I knew that, I wouldn't
be in debt to begin with!
If you're too busy, I can go for you!
I mean, if it's not too
dangerous a place, that is.
Yeah, well, uh...
We want to crush Thousand Tricks,
but it's not like we can
just storm their clan HQ.
Guess we'll just have to lie in wait
somewhere and jump him when he's alone.
Yeah.
You're...
Who are you?
Damn you!
Thanks for the warm welcome
the other day, Thousand Tricks.
You've got some balls showing
yourself like this.
Now I remember!
The pub incident.
Took you long enough!
You wanna go?
Even though I warned you he's a god?!
What? You're...
Out of the way, sweet cheeks.
Our quarrel is with Thousand Tricks.
Let's all calm down.
I understand why you're angry.
Liz's attack caught you completely off guard.
I get it.
But look, Tino and I are on a date.
I don't want to fight.
If you want an apology, I'll do it.
I'll even get on my knees.
Master! You cannot get on your knees!
These jerks aren't worth your...
Besides, today I'm unarmed, you see.
So why don't we table this?
Beating me when I'm not at my best
won't satisfy you either, right?
Master is a god!
He's just worried that you'll get beaten
to a pulp and lose your confidence!
Are you really so stupid that
you don't realize that?!
What... did you say?
Tino, go easy.
We wanted to get something sweet, right?
We don't have time for this.
That's right! Master doesn't
have time for you!
So get that through your skulls, go wash
your dirty hick faces, and try again.
Tino!
Let's calm down.
Tino?
Er, anyway... how about we all
just walk away from this?
I... think not!
Fine. Fine.
If we're going to do this,
then let's do it right.
What's going on?
A fight?
Looks like it's hunters!
What the hell is he doing?
Drawing all this attention
in a place like this.
I don't know.
But don't be careless.
Yes, sir!
It's two against six.
There's Arnold and then his
followers A through E.
I thought there would be some other
clan members on this big street,
but it looks like nobody's around.
Hey!
How long are you going to space out?!
Let's get this started, Level 8!
Sorry about that, A.
How the hell do you know my name?!
Eyyy?
Eigh, don't let him rile you up.
Aye.
Just like the rumors said,
you're a slippery bastard.
But I know.
Your combat power doesn't quite
correspond to your level.
You're a fool with no skills of your own
who climbed the ranks through
luck and the skills of your friends.
That's the truth behind Thousand Tricks.
Any objections?
Yeah.
I'm not mature enough to stand
by idly while you insult Master.
Huh. I like that look in her eyes.
She's going to be strong one day.
However...
Girlie, while I'll admit
that you've got spirit,
you're completely out of your league.
We have no quarrel with you.
Shut up!
Master, please allow me.
I'm going to make them regret this.
If you must.
Take care!
Huh? What?
You're not... stopping her?
Nope.
If it's what you want...
They're in your hands.
Y-Yes, Master...
Shall we call it off?
How dare you make fun of my Master!
This is odd.
You'd think Ark's team, or someone
from Obsidian Cross,
or a member of Starlight
would pass by here...
Hey!
Don't look away!
That girlie's fighting for you!
Oh, right.
Watch me properly, Master!
Got it.
Go, Tino!
You're the bestest Tino in the world!
Stop with the weird cheers!
You almost got him!
Just a little more, and you've got him!
I've had it with your mockery,
Thousand Tricks!
You make a lower rank fight for
you, and then to add insult to injury,
you tell her she almost has me?!
Do you imagine yourself to be some
king, giving orders from on high?
Answer me, Thousand Tricks!
I don't think I'm any kind of king,
but you leave me no choice.
I just didn't want to fight you, is all.
What's that?!
I won't go so far as to kill you.
What?
Brother, what are you even talking about?
A spell that can subdue high-level
hunters without killing them,
has a wide range,
and affects nobody but your chosen targets?!
You're asking for way too much!
Yeah... I figured even you couldn't do it.
I'll see what I can do!
You bastard! Wh-What is this?
Gravity magic.
It's called the Tyrant's Order.
It's an original spell.
Impressive, huh?
M-Master...
Please... help me...
I'm sorry!
Here, pull...
Master...
You bastard!
So you're a mage?
Nope.
But that doesn't matter.
Arnold, if you still want
to fight me after this,
I'll set some conditions.
Condi...tions...?!
I am the First Steps's clan master.
So you have to work your way up to me.
Our top parties are Obsidian Cross,
Starlight, and Ark Brave.
If you defeat all three of them, then
I'll consider accepting your challenge.
Damn you.. Thousand Tricks!
I'm so sorry.
I couldn't meet your expectations...
There's nothing to be sorry about.
I'm the one who misread the situation.
Above a certain point,
I don't have a clue about a
hunter's level or strength.
I'm so useless.
I don't deserve to eat this cake.
That's not true at all.
Master, please!
Give me a chance to redeem myself!
Please tell me where I can find a
treasure vault with a valuable relic!
I promise to bring in enough
to clear your ten-digit debt!
Well... uh...
That's so hard!
Si, it broke!
I don't want this replica, anyway.
Bring that annoying, huge thing!
What do you want me to do?
The Institute for Relic Research
is full of stubborn people.
Even Krai couldn't do anything about it.
Kill, kill, kill.
Damn.
Guess we're done for today, then.
Oh, yeah. Speaking of Krai...
I heard he was attacked by Arnold.
But I also heard that Ti took the guy on.
Krai sure is a tough master!
I don't think Ti could beat that guy, though.
So what happened?
Looks like in the end, Krai
used the Tyrant's Order.
Oh, the spell that Lucia was bitching about.
So what do you think, Sis?
Should we crush him?
I think it's fine.
As long as Krai doesn't order it, anyway.
Right?
Sorry to bother you about every little thing.
Not at all.
Verifying the truth is also part of my job.
I don't really get why,
but Arnold and his gang are super mad.
He's a hunter who rose to
level 7 by slaying a dragon.
But then you acted like he
wasn't even worth remembering,
and after that, you asked him to hunt
a thunder dragon so you could make teriyaki.
You were provoking him, right?
Not at all!
I never put in such a request,
and everyone knows that for
teriyaki, chicken is much tastier.
So I don't need the thunder dragon anymore.
I see.
So you're retracting the request,
because chicken is tastier anyway.
Are you fanning the flames?
No!
Please tell Arnold and his friends that I'll
never forget about them until I forget.
You really want to forget about them, huh?
No.
I mean, I won't forget them
as long as I remember.
So from your perspective as a level 8,
what was your impression of Arnold?
If I had to say...
Big, rough...
Go home, brat.
...and likes big boobs, I guess?
I'm sorry?
No, that's just speculation.
Forget it.
U-Um!
Yes?
Actually, there's something
I'd like to ask you about.
The reason I failed my entrance
exam here three years ago...
Huh? Three years ago?
Back then, I was completely
defeated by Luke.
But I was told I had promise.
You're the one who said I didn't
make the cut by a hair!
Please tell me!
What was I lacking?
I don't even have to answer that.
I'm sure you've already
figured it out yourself.
Huh?
If nothing else, if you tried
again today, you'd pass for sure.
But you don't have any
intention of joining us.
You feel fulfilled working
for the Association.
You ought to cherish the life you have now.
Not to mention,
there are a ton of hunters who
look forward to seeing you there.
Now I remember the reason she failed.
Back then, she was still only fourteen.
Chloe Welter
14 years old
Just under the minimum age...
She hadn't turned fifteen yet.
Besides, if were to poach Chloe now,
Gark would beat the crap out of me.
Krai didn't give me a straight answer.
This might be another one of
the famous Thousand Trials.
"An answer is worthless
if it's just given to you."
"You've got to find it for yourself."
That's what his back seemed to be saying.
I guess I'll keep trying
to find the real answer.
The day I discover it deep
inside me will come for sure.
Right now, I have a duty as the receptionist
of the Explorers' Association.
And that is to be of help to
the hunters who come here.
Hello, and welcome to the Association!
We have come from the Land of Fog!
By: Thunder Dragon of the Fog - Yes, Falling Fog
We are from Nebulanubes!
But hold on a minute!
Stifled Shadow beat us up!
Thousand Tricks crushed us!
On top of that, we got summoned
by the Association?!
Next time on Let This Grieving Soul...
Retire!
Episode 12
If Possible, I'd Like to Get It
What are you plotting?!
"If Possible, I'd Like to Get It."